Bailey and Thurman families papers, circa 1882-1995
Emory University
- Printed material, 1885-1986, Series 4; Box 4 (folders 30-59) - Box 5 and OP1-2
  - Steadwell, B. S. (ed.), The Children’s Code of Morals, La Crosse, Wisconsin: The Light, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Southwestern Creek and Seminole District, Sunday School Convention, Proceedings of the Ninth Annual Session, July 24-27, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Thurman, Sue Bailey, Pioneers of Negro Origin in California (1949) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Turner, Nephronia (Mrs.), Memorial Service, March 17, 1929 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Vining, Elizabeth Gray, Anthology with Comments, Wallingford, Pennsylvania: Pendle Hill, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Washington, Little J.L: The Walking Bible and Prodigy, broadside, n.d. (Box OP23)
  - Webb, Walter Jr., M.D., Memorial Service, February 5, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - "Where Are My Children?," Advertisement, Hiawatha Theatre, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Williams, Ralph C, The Story of Amos’ Fortune (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Woman’s American Baptist Home Mission Society, Tidings, February 1911 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Woman's Convention, Auxiliary to the National Baptist Convention, receipt, Louisville, Kentucky, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Women Chicot County Association, Program of the Second Annual Session, August 11-13, 1898 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Women’s Southeast District Association, First Annual Session, July 23-25, 1897, Little Rock: Vanguard Print, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Newspaper clippings
  - Obituaries, Bailey family (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - "Among Colored People" (About Susie Bailey) (3 copies) (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Hope, October 1893 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Article: Nannie Burroughs, "The Training School Situation." (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Howard Thurman to begin teaching at University of Iowa (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Sue Bailey Thurman 1937 Lecture Series (2 copies) (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Sue Bailey Thurman to attend Townsend Affair (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Family related clippings (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - "Meta Fuller Dies at 90" (1968) (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Miscellaneous clippings (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Newspapers
  - Arkansas Survey, n.d (Box OP1, Folder 1)
  - Baptist Vanguard, April 28, 1893 (Box OP1, Folder 2)
  - Baptist Vanguard, August 11, 1893 (Box OP1, Folder 2)
  - Baptist Vanguard, March 31, 1898 (Box OP1, Folder 2)
  - Baptist Vanguard, May 2, 1898 (Box OP1, Folder 2)
  - The Guardian, June 30, 1906 (Box OP1, Folder 3)
  - Hope, July 1892 (Box OP1, Folder 4)
  - Hope, December 1895 (Box OP1, Folder 4)
  - Mission Herald, May 1916 (Box OP1, Folder 5)
  - Pine Bluff Weekly Herald, May 18, 1901 (Box OP1, Folder 6)
  - Southeast Advocate, August 29, 1907 (Box OP1, Folder 7)
  - St. Louis Weekly Globe Democrat, September 12, 1889 (Box OP2, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Weekly Globe Democrat, December 8, 1896 (Box OP2, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Weekly Globe Democrat, December 11, 1896 (Box OP2, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Weekly Globe Democrat, December 13, 1896 (Box OP2, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Weekly Globe Democrat, December 15, 1896 (Box OP2, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Weekly Globe Democrat, December 18, 1896 (Box OP2, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Weekly Globe Democrat, December 22, 1896 (Box OP2, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Weekly Globe Democrat, January 5, 1897 (Box OP2, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Weekly Globe Democrat, January 8, 1897 (Box OP2, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Weekly Globe Democrat, September 10, 1901 (Box OP2, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Weekly Globe Democrat, September 13, 1901 (Box OP2, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Weekly Globe Democrat, September 17, 1901 (Box OP2, Folder 1)
  - St. Louis Weekly Globe Democrat, September 20, 1901 (Box OP2, Folder 1)
  - The Union, September 2, 1948 (Box OP2, Folder 2)
- Photographs, Series 5; Boxes 6 - 11; OP 3-14 and 18
  - Family
  - I. G. Bailey (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - I. G. Bailey, large framed portrait (Box OP18)
  - Susie Bailey (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Susie Bailey and Scott Ford (brother) with charges/students (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - I. G. Bailey, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - I. G. Bailey, Jr., portrait (Box OP3)
  - I. G. Bailey, Jr., Omega Psi Phi Fraternity, 1915-1916 (Box OP4)
  - Extended family (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Sue Bailey Thurman, alone [Image 0807-003] (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Sue Bailey Thurman with Gandhi in India [See also Travel: Various photos from India] [Image 0807-001] (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Sue Bailey Thurman, attending various functions (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sue Bailey Thurman, attending various functions (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Thurman family home (Childhood home) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Howard Thurman, alone (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Howard Thurman, alone (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Howard Thurman, alone (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Howard Thurman, alone (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Howard Thurman, alone (Box OP5)
  - Howard Thurman, alone (candid) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Howard Thurman, alone (candid) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Howard Thurman, alone (Religious dress) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Howard Thurman, group photographs, early career (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Howard Thurman, group photographs, middle career (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Howard Thurman, group photographs, middle career (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Howard Thurman, group photographs, middle career (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Howard Thurman, group photographs, middle career (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Howard Thurman, group photographs, later career (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Howard Thurman, group photograph, taken at Testimonial dinner in honor of Dr. William Hinton, Boston, Mass., February 10, 1954 [Dr.. Thurman guest at the head table] (Box OP6)
  - Howard Thurman, group photographs, religious proceedings (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Howard and Sue Bailey Thurman alone (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Howard and Sue Bailey Thurman attending various functions (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Anne Thurman (Box OP7)
  - Bailey and Thurman family photographs (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Bailey and Thurman family photographs (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Bailey and Thurman family photographs (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Bailey and Thurman family photographs (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Bailey and Thurman family photographs (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Bailey and Thurman family photographs (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Universities/Churches
  - Howard University (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Howard University (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Howard University, African American college students meeting [Howard University representatives include Thurman] (Box OP8)
  - Howard University Choir, Rankin Chapel [Thurman on right] (Box OP9)
  - Howard University Committee [Thurman not pictured] (Box OP10)
  - Morehouse College, San Francisco Bay Area Alumni Chapter Awards Dinner (1969) [Dr. Thurman guest of honor] (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Morehouse College, Howard Thurman birthday celebration (1983) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Morehouse College, Dedication of Howard Thurman Tower of Bells (1995) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Morehouse College, 1995 Dedication Ceremony, Sue Bailey Thurman and Coretta Scott King in attendance (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Spelman University (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Spelman University students (Box OP11)
  - Bennett College (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Boston University, group photographs with Howard Thurman (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Boston University, group photographs with Howard Thurman (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Boston University, group photographs with Sue Bailey Thurman (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Boston University, group photographs without the Thurmans (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Boston University, group photographs without the Thurmans (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Boston University, group photographs without the Thurmans (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Boston University, lecture [speaker unknown] (Box OP12)
  - Boston University, contemporary photographs of students and campus (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Fellowship Church gatherings (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Fellowship Church gatherings (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Fellowship Church gatherings (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Fellowship Church gatherings (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Fellowship Church programs (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Travel
  - Various photos from India (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Various travels including trip to Egypt [Image 0807-002] (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Various landscapes (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Travel slides (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Travel slides (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Photographs from Sue Bailey Thurman’s Pioneers of Negro Origin in California (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of others
  - Sister Joanna Moore, portrait (Box OP13)
  - Photographs of well-known African Americans (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of well-known African Americans (Box OP14)
  - Wedding photographs (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of others (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of others (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of others (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of others (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Photographs of others (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Photographs of others (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of others (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of others (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous
  - Various negatives and slides (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Various proofs (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - (Box 11 3, Folder Photocopied pictures with identification)
  - Artistic Displays by or about Howard Thurman (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, Works of Art (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, Paintings, Sculptures, Sketches (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Black history (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - DuSable Museum (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - M. Gandhi Memorial (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous photographs (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous photographs, (floral arrangements, furniture, etc.) (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Legal and financial records, Series 6; Box 12 (folder 1-7)
  - Receipts (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Insurance policies (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Contracts (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Real estate records (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Real estate records (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Bank statements (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Certificates/Membership information to various organizations (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Ephemera, Series 7; Box 12 (folders 8-18) and OP 15-17, 19-22
  - Book(s) of Devotional Words about Mothers (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Memorabilia from 14th Annual Session of the National Baptist Women’s Convention (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Campaign pin with Abe Lincoln’s picture attached (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Scholarship record- I. G. Bailey Jr. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous items (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous items (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Book list (By Departments) school not identified (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous writings (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous "Letter to Jesus" (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Assorted addressed/empty envelopes (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Cloth map of Palestine (Box OP15)
  - Cloth map of Western Asia (Box OP16)
  - Framed diploma for Josephine Ella Jamison from Industrial University, Branch Normal College (Isaac Bailey, Sr.’s Alma Mater), 1893 (Box OP17)
  - Scrapbook given to Howard Thurman (Box OP19)
  - Scrapbook kept by Howard and Sue Bailey Thurman (re: Trip to India) (Box OP20)
  - Cassette recording (Nathan I. Huggins Memorial Service) (Box OP21)
  - Miniature Book of Hymns (Box OP22)
- Collected material, Series 8; Box 13
  - Slides and negatives of Sue Bailey Thurmond and family [Acc. 2004-06-02] (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Slides and negatives of Sue Bailey Thurmond and family [Acc. 2004-06-02] (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Audiovisual material, Series 9
  - Coretta Scott King, Sue Thurman, and Howard Thurman conversation, July 11, 1979 [1 of 3] (Box CD1)
  - Coretta Scott King, Sue Thurman, and Howard Thurman conversation, July 11, 1979 [2 of 3] (Box CD2)
  - Coretta Scott King, Sue Thurman, and Howard Thurman conversation, July 11, 1979 [3 of 3] (Box CD3)